Wake up, Lord Darren.
Count Carter is his father,
and Redmond is his brother.
They know Severin’s true worth
better than anyone.
If he wasn’t worthless,
I never would have
publicly broken the
engagement.
Look, Lord Darren.
These are the lowlife friends he
hangs around with in the mines.
He actually brought such filthy
scum to desecrate the Holy Cathedral!
Enough!
I know Lord Severin far
better than any of you idiots.
Get out of Emeraldstone
while you still can.
Darren, you would side
with this traitor against
every noble in
Emeraldstone?
Don't forget
House Carter
stands behind the
Morellan family,
head of the Four Great Families!
Exactly, Darren.
In front of the Morellan family,
you’re not even worth
a toe.
Since you all rely so
heavily on the
Morellan family,
why don’t you
summon them right now?
Let’s see if
they dare touch me.
Since you’re so eager to die,
I’ll contact the Lord
of Morellan right now.
Lady Elowen Morellan, heir of
the Morellan family,
has arrive!
It's actually Lady Elowen,
the greatest beauty of Golantis.
Lady Elowen!
Thank you for
gracing my son’s wedding.
Which son?
Redmond, come greet Lady Elowen.
Lady Elowen…
Get lost.
She said get out.
Are you deaf?
Lady Elowen told you
to leave, move!
Elowen Morellan, heir
of the Morellan family,
brings the core
treasuries of my bloodline.
Lord Severin...
please accept me as your wife.
Present the gifts!
Yes, my lady.
Thirty-six fortified castles
and all their endless
territories under
Morellan rule.
The Morellan family’s
dragon crystal mines and
ten top-tier heavy armor forges.
The keys to the
four great Morellan treasuries.
Fifty percent command
over the Morellan family’s
one hundred thousand
iron cavalry, effective
immediately.
What? Directly sending it to the Vault?
Half the entire Morellan family…
handed over just like that.